Priscilla Monteiro Rangel da Fonseca

pmonteirorf@gmail.com

Highgate, Perth WA

Summary

I am a full stack developer with over eight years of experience. I have worked on legacy application maintenance and the development of new features. My technical skills include Java, PHP, WEB API, React Native, AngularJS, JavaScript, jQuery, Bootstrap, HTML5, CSS 3.0, JUnit, MySQL, and MVC.

Seeking a developer position where I can utilize my skills and abilities to contribute to the growth of the company and the team. I am open to learning new technologies and skills and am keen on contributing to the success of the company and the team.

Experience

Full Stack Developer at Radix Engineering & Software

July 2021 - February 2023

- Radix Engineering is a consulting company based in Brazil with numerous clients. I worked with two of them as a Full Stack Developer, utilizing both agile and waterfall methodologies. I collaborated with the team to develop various projects within the company, always prioritizing the swift delivery of features while maintaining a focus on quality. During my time there, I employed a variety of technologies, including:
 - o Java 8 and PHP 7
 - o React Native and Angular
 - HTML, CSS, JavaScript, jQuery, Bootstrap
 - WEB APIs
 - Oracle and MySQL databases
 - JUnit and Mockito

System Analyst at Bradesco Seguros

November 2017 - June 2021

- Bradesco Seguros is one of the largest health insurance companies in Latin America. As a Systems
 Analyst, I played a crucial role in enhancing the company's legacy system and implementing new
 features. Additionally, I took on responsibilities such as leading and managing projects, providing
 technical support, identifying and resolving bugs, and creating and executing test cases. My skill set
 includes:
 - o Java 7
 - o HTML, CSS, JavaScript, jQuery
 - MVC architecture
 - Oracle database
 - o Project leadership and management
 - Writing business and technical specifications
 - Test case development
 - Technical support

System Analyst at Capgemini

February 2015 - October 2017

- Capgemini is a global leader in partnership with a wide range of clients worldwide. During my time, I
 collaborated on numerous projects for Bradesco Seguros, offering solutions, writing business and
 technical specifications, and actively contributing to program code development. My key responsibilities
 and skills included:
 - o Java 7
 - HTML, CSS, JavaScript, jQuery
 - Writing business and technical specifications
 - Test case development

Priscilla Monteiro Rangel da Fonseca

Java Software Developer at Senior Solution

October 2014 – January 2015

- Senior Solution was a leading company in software development and technology services for the financial sector in Brazil. During my tenure, I specialized in developing new features and maintaining the system, employing technologies such as:
 - o Java 7
 - Technical support

Web Designer at SMARTSIS - Sistemas, Informática e Automação LTDA

March 2014 - September 2014

- Smartsis is a company focused on software development for the taxi industry. During my time, I worked on website creation for taxi cooperatives, including designing layouts for applications and all visual materials for clients and the company, using the technologies:
 - o HTML, CSS, JavaScript, jQuery, Bootstrap
 - Elaboration of a prototype for web and app screens
 - Creation of graphic materials

Software Developer Internship at Stefanini

November 2012 - February 2014

- Stefanini is a global group of Brazilian origin, specializing in guiding clients through the digital transformation of their businesses. I contributed to the development of systems for Caixa Econômica Federal, one of Brazil's oldest and largest banks, in the housing sector. I was involved in development and requirements gathering, using the following technologies:
 - o Java 7
 - o HTML, CSS, JavaScript, JSF
 - JUnit and Mockito
 - Writing business and technical specifications

Education & Training

General English Language Links International	Apr/2023 – Oct/2023
Postgraduate Faculdade de Educação Tecnológica do Rio de Janeiro — FAETERJ-Rio Course: Metrology and Quality Applied to Software	Jan/2014 - Nov/2015
Graduate Faculdade de Educação Tecnológica do Rio de Janeiro — FAETERJ-Rio Course: Analysis of Systems - Graduation Date: February /2014	Jan/2010 - Nov/2013
Framework Symfony Alura	2021
Java 8: Discover what's new in this version Alura	2021
Spring Boot API Alura	2020
SOA Training - Service Oriented Architecture Gigante Consultoria	2020

Priscilla Monteiro Rangel da Fonseca

Java Spring Framework Training Caelum	2019
Object-Oriented Java Training Stefanini Knowledge Solutions	2013
HIBERNATE Training Stefanini Knowledge Solutions	2013

Languages_

English – *B1 Level* Portuguese – *Native*